casebriefs.com 2019-07-16

# Privacy | Casebriefs

### Privacy

 **Casebriefs.com takes privacy seriously.**

We ask you to provide information that we need in order to deliver the service you have requested, and to help determine how we can improve our products and services. We do not share the information you have given us without your explicit permission to do so. Most areas of our site are accessible without registration of any kind.

The Company respects the privacy of the users of the Service and is committed to reasonably protect it in all respects. The information about the user as collected by the Company is: (a) information supplied by users and (b) information automatically tracked while navigation (c) information collected from any other source (collectively referred to as Information).

 **1\. INFORMATION RECEIVED, COLLECTED AND STORED BY THE COMPANY**

A. INFORMATION SUPPLIED BY USERS  
**• Registration data:**  
When you register on the website, Application and for the Service, we ask that you provide basic contact Information such as your name, sex, age, address, pin code, contact number, occupation, interests and email address etc. When you register using your other accounts like on Facebook, Twitter, Gmail etc. we shall retrieve Information from such account to continue to interact with you and to continue providing the Service.  
**• Voluntary information:**  
We may collect additional information at other times, including but not limited to, when you provide feedback, change your content or email preferences, respond to a survey, or communicate with us.

B. INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED/ TRACKED WHILE NAVIGATION  
**• Cookies:**  
To improve the responsiveness of the “Application” for our users, we may use “cookies”, or similar electronic tools to collect information to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User ID) to understand the user’s individual interests using the identified computer. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we do not control. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us via website, Application or Service though your computer/laptop/netbook or mobile/tablet/pad/handheld device etc.

 **• Log File Information:**  
We automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, mobile number, including your IP address, when you visit our site, application or service. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data — such as the pages you view. We automatically receive and log information from your browser, including your IP address, your computer’s name, your operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed. We may also collect log information from your device, including your location, IP address, your device’s name, device’s serial number or unique identification number (e.g.. UDiD on your iOS device), your device operating system, browser type and version, CPU speed, and connection speed etc.

 **• Information from other Sources:**  
We may receive information about you from other sources, add it to our account information and treat it in accordance with this policy. If you provide information to the platform provider or other partner, whom we provide services, your account information and order information may be passed on to us. We may obtain updated contact information from third parties in order to correct our records and fulfil the Service or to communicate with you.

 **• Demographic and purchase information:**  
We may reference other sources of demographic and other information in order to provide you with more targeted communications and promotions.

 **2\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES / AD-SERVERS**  
The Application may include links to other websites or applications. Such websites or applications are governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control. Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the application, you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can’t find the privacy policy of any of these sites via a link from the application’s homepage, you should contact the application owners directly for more information.

When we present information to our advertisers — to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites or Applications — it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages / content within our websites or Applications.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our websites or Applications. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number or other personally identifiable information) about your visits to this and other websites or application, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  We do not provide any personally identifiable information to third party websites / advertisers / ad-servers without your consent.

 **3\. INFORMATION USE BY THE COMPANY**  
The Information as supplied by the users enables us to improve the Service and provide you the most user-friendly experience. In some cases/provision of certain service(s) or utility(ies), we may require your contact address as well. All required information is service dependent and the Company may use the above said user Information to, maintain, protect, and improve the Service (including advertising on the “Application”) and for developing new services. Any personally identifiable information provided by you will not be considered as sensitive if it is freely available and / or accessible in the public domain like any comments, messages, blogs, scribbles available on social platforms like facebook, twitter etc.

Any posted/uploaded/conveyed/communicated by users on the public sections of the “Application” becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.  
In case you choose to decline to submit personally identifiable information on the Service, we may not be able to provide certain services to you. We will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the same at the time of opening your account. In any case, we will not be liable and or responsible for the denial of certain services to you for lack of you providing the necessary personal information.  
When you register with the Service, we contact you from time to time about updation of your personal information to provide the users such features that we believe may benefit / interest you.

 **4\. INFORMATION SHARING**  
The Company shares your information with any third party without obtaining the prior consent of the User in the following limited circumstances:  
a) When it is requested or required by law or by any court or governmental agency or authority to disclose, for the purpose of verification of identity, or for the prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, or for prosecution and punishment of offences. These disclosures are made in good faith and belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary for enforcing these Terms or for complying with the applicable laws and regulations.  
b) The Company proposes to share such information within its group companies and officers and employees of such group companies for the purpose of processing personal information on its behalf. We also ensure that these recipients of such information agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
c) The Company may present information to our advertisers – to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites or Applications – however it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our site.  
d) The Company may share your information regarding your activities on websites or Applications with third party social websites to populate your social wall that is visible to other people however you will have an option to set your privacy settings, where you can decide what you would like to share or not to share with others.

 **5\. ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
When you use the Service Site we make good faith efforts to provide you, as and when requested by you, with access to your personal information and shall further ensure that any personal information or sensitive personal data or information found to be inaccurate or deficient shall be corrected or amended as feasible, subject to any requirement for such personal information or sensitive personal data or information to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems.

 **6\. INFORMATION SECURITY**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. All information gathered securely stored within the Company controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit or use our website, mobile application or services. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits or use to particular website, mobile application or services, in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **7\. UPDATES / CHANGES**  
We may alter our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary changes in technology, applicable law or any other variant. In any case, we reserve the right to change (at any point of time) the terms of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use. Any changes we make will be effective immediately on notice, which we may give by posting the new policy on the “Service”. Your use of the Service after such notice will be deemed acceptance of such changes. We may also make reasonable efforts to inform you via electronic mail. In any case, you are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically on the “Application”) to ensure that you are aware of the latest version.

Casebriefs would like to contact you from time to time to ask you about your experience with our products and services. You may not believe it, but we really do care what you think. We know you’re busy with school, so sometimes we might run a small sweepstakes for free stuff, just to say thanks for taking the time to answer our questions. Casebriefs will also contact you with important information about features – for example, a new set of interactive tools or new valuable content updates and additions.

If you would like to contact us in regard to anything in this site or about privacy rights, please feel free to send an email to: [info@Casebriefs.com](mailto:info@Casebriefs.com)

Thank you, and good luck in school!
